<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Project Astal</title><link href="http://arcxon.github.io/project-astal/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://arcxon.github.io/project-astal/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://arcxon.github.io/project-astal/</id><updated>2016-04-14T10:20:00+05:30</updated><entry><title>The Mystery of Zulibi</title><link href="http://arcxon.github.io/project-astal/the-mystery-of-zulibi.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2016-04-14T10:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>AdiUltra</name></author><id>tag:arcxon.github.io,2016-04-14:project-astal/the-mystery-of-zulibi.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;by : Ananya Singh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drake woke up and found himself in a dark place. It was cold and damp. He could feel the moisture on the walls of the room. He saw a faint light and started walking towards it, the faint light was coming from full moon which was right above him. He went out and walked a bit distance. He heard the rustling of leaves behind him and he tumbled. He had goosebumps all over his body, he couldn't get the courage in him to look what was behind him. Suddenly he felt a hand on his back, his shoulders shot up to his ears. He turned hoping to see a ghost or monster but he was relaxed to find that it was his sister, Julia at the back of him. Their eyes fixed on each other, trying to understand what had happened to both of them. They couldn't remember how they had reached this dark place, they had only glimpses of recent memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;They had boarded a ship; it had sunk; they remembered the screams of their parents and everything would become blurred after that.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They held each others hands and started finding their way out of that place. But however hard they tried, they reached the dark room again and again. after  being tired they decided to rest on a huge tree whose branches were broad enough to let them lie on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the sun shone in the morning they woke up immediately and came down the tree. Drake tried to use the shadow of a stick to find the direction but there were too many trees to obstruct proper sunlight. They were loosing their hope to return home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;" Drake do you know how did we reach here? "&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;" No sis, i can not remember how did we come here, maybe the sea waves had drifted us here......I think it is not a lonely island because i have seen footprints of animals. "&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;" I hope we soon find a way out of this creepy place. "&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;" I too hope so.......lets keep trying. "&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drake and Julia both at their wits end and sat down under a tree to take rest. They were going to fall asleep but suddenly they heard a noise of footsteps, they opened their eyes and saw a wild dog roaming around them, first they got worried but when they saw the dog going away from them harmlessly they decided to follow it in case they could find some safe place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After an hour or two of following the dog they started hearing the sound of sea waves hitting the rocks, they got excited and a spark of hope burned inside their hearts. finally they reached the beach and were delighted to see the setting sun in front of them and the open sea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drake climbed up a tree to see if he could find a ship in the see or a safe place on the island. He shouted back to Julia, " I can spot a many lamps burning at a height, i think it is a palace, lets go and check it out. "&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he didn't get any response from her sister he glanced back and was shocked to see three huge dogs circling around her&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>The Visit</title><link href="http://arcxon.github.io/project-astal/the-visit.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2016-04-14T10:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>AdiUltra</name></author><id>tag:arcxon.github.io,2016-04-14:project-astal/the-visit.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I was a very successful bussiness man till today, till this exact moment. I always feared that my past would visit me. My past will be the reason for my fall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I was wrong, very wrong. Now My future haunts me. And now When I know what I will do, I really feel that my past was way better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel dazed when I see myself standing before me. I am young, in my mid-20s and the person before me is 30 years older, has my same exact face, features and attitude. The only difference is that he has flanks of white hair in his jet black hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has told me moments ago that I will become the worst hated man in the future. And also scientifically most successful. I would win four Nobel Prizes Three in physics and one in chemistry. But then I would create the most destructive weapon in the universe, An annihilation bomb. The combination of Anti-matter and matter, creating energy far beyond the scope of nuclear reactions used in Nuclear bombs. And I would explode three of them. Wiping half of the population of earth, destroying most of Europe and parts of Asia and Africa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What he next told me was the current issue for worrying. The countries that were left by the explosion took pledge to destroy me and my every research. They formed a syndicate to exterminate from the face of the world. They had all the scientists left after the D day. But I was also a one man Army. I created the elixir for immortality that allowed me to escape all the attempts made to assassinate me. But soon they figured my immortality So, they created a time machine, Using my own theories to kill me before I could be immortal.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>